{
    "subject": "resource/The_War_Zone",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Freddie_Cunliffe",
    "human_readable": "Freddie Cunliffe stars in The War Zone.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7413909435272217,
            "question": "Name a movie starring Freddie Cunliffe."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.659317672252655,
            "question": "Is Freddie Cunliffe an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6453108787536621,
            "question": "Who stars in the movie 'The War Zone'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5210821628570557,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie Freddie Cunliffe appeared in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4309501349925995,
            "question": "Are there any other notable actors in 'The War Zone'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3209667503833771,
            "question": "Who directed 'The War Zone'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2711411118507385,
            "question": "What awards has 'The War Zone' won?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2509896457195282,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of 'The War Zone'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22275635600090027,
            "question": "When was 'The War Zone' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17814423143863678,
            "question": "What genre is 'The War Zone' likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Freddie Cunliffe stars in The War Zone.",
            "html": "dbpedia_228_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'The War Zone' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_228_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of 'The War Zone'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_228_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What awards has 'The War Zone' won?",
            "html": "dbpedia_228_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_228_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_228_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_228_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_228_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_228_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_228_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_228_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_228_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_228_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_228_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Freddie Cunliffe's acting roles, including his participation in the film \"The War Zone\" (also known as \"The War Zone,\" 1999). Therefore, the statement \"Freddie Cunliffe stars in The War Zone\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}